aboutsla.com 2014-08-15

# Term of Service - AboutsLA

**Privacy Policy**

**This Privacy Policy applies to our sites.**

This Policy describes how we treat personal information. Any capitalized terms we don’t define in this policy are defined in our Terms and Conditions.

**We collect information from and about you.**

**Contact Information.**  For example, we collect your name and email address if you register on our site. We might also collect your mailing address.

**Information You Submit or Post.**  We collect the information you post in a public space on our site. We also collect information when you contact us. 

**Other Information.**  If you use our sites, we may collect information about the browser you’re using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us.

**We get information about you from third parties.**  For example, social media platforms may also give us information about you. This might include getting information from social media plugins. Affiliates or other business partners may also give us information. This might include information they gathered passively.

**We use information as disclosed and described here.**

**We use information to improve our products and services.**  We may use your information to make our Sites better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us or understand your preferences. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties. 

**We use information for security purposes.**  We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites.

**We use information for marketing purposes.**  For example, when you register with our sites we might send you information about special offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. If you register with us, we’ll enroll you to receive our emails. We may send this information by email. 

**We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship.**  We may contact you about your account or feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

**We use information as otherwise permitted by law.**

**We may share information with third parties.**

**We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.**  For example, we share information with vendors who send emails for us. We may also share information with companies that operate our websites or run a promotion.

**We will share information with our business partners.**  This includes sharing for marketing or advertising purposes. For example, we will share information with Affiliate Stores to process orders or understand preferences. Or we might share information that third parties can use to serve you with ads they think you will like. This could include sharing with our partners what ads you look at. Third parties may use information for their own marketing or advertising purposes. 

**We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.**  For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud.

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.**  For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

**We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.**

**You have certain choices about sharing and marketing practices.**

**You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails.**  To stop receiving our promotional emails, log into your Account and update your "Account setting." Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions. If you receive promotional emails from a third party, you will need to separately opt-out with them.

**Your California privacy rights.**

If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please send us an [email](mailto:%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy92113%20=%20'aboutsla'%20+%20'@';%20addy92113%20=%20addy92113%20+%20'gmail'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy92113%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy92113\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E), 

**These Sites and children.**

Our sites is meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can [email](mailto:%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy77448%20=%20'aboutsla'%20+%20'@';%20addy77448%20=%20addy77448%20+%20'gmail'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy77448%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy77448\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E) us. 

**We store information in the United States.**

Information we maintain is stored within the United States. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country.

**We use standard security measures.**

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.

We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

**You can update your information.**

To update your information, log into the site and click the "Account Setting" link.

**We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site we don’t control.**

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites. Our site may also serve third party content that contains their own cookies or tracking technologies. To learn more, click here. We do not control the use of those technologies. We also do not control the privacy practices of our Affiliate Stores. This includes their use of cookies and other tracking technologies.

**Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at:

Email: [aboutsla@gmail.com](mailto:aboutsla@gmail.com)

**Password Reset Sent!**

Look in your e-mail for your password reset notification from aboutsla.com. If you don't see the e-mail in your inbox, please check your spam folder.

You must click the link from the email to reset your password. If you do not receive this email or have additional questions, please [contact us](http://aboutsla.com/pages.aspx?ticks=130909213207394)

Return to [Login Page ](http://aboutsla.com/index.php/user-login)

By using the AboutsLA.com [Site](http://www.aboutsla.com/), you agree that you have read and you understand, and consent to the following Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy, in their entirety including any updates that may be posted on Site from time to time. The Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference in this Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to these agreements and policies do NOT use the AboutsLA.com Site. AboutsLA.com reserves the right to revise this Terms and Conditions, at its sole and absolute discretion, by updating this posting. The revised terms will take effect the date they are posted on the AboutsLA.com Site. Your continued use of the AboutsLA.com Site shall be deemed to be your acceptance of the modified terms. Please review these posted terms on a regular basis.

If you need any assistance with the Site, please contact customer service at [aboutsla@gmail.com](mailto:aboutsla@gmail.com)
